Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: 10/12/2019

Privacy Policy
--------------

This Privacy Policy constitutes an agreement between you and Hackerwars.io ("Hackerwars.io", "Hacker Wars", "we", "us", "staff", "admin") regarding your access to and use of Hackerwars.io as well as any other media forms, channels, mobile website, channels, or other Hacker Wars material linked or connected (collectively termed the "site" and/or "Hackerwars.io").

We are committed and take seriously the duty of protecting your privacy and personal information. We will never sell your personal data nor will we abuse it to find out more information about you, other than what is used to play the game. If you ever have any questions or comments regarding this policy or anything privacy or security related, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or [\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

In this policy, we will seek to describe to the best of our ability how we collect, use, and our boundary rights in regards to your information. We ask that you take the time to read this policy carefully along with our Terms of Service and Use.

### Read this policy carefully.

### What Personal information do we collect?

At an overview, we collect information that you voluntarily provide us when registering such as your email, password, alias, security and host identifying data. We also collect any information that you upload such as in-game emails, profile pictures, and comments.

Information that we collect can vary depending on what you provide us but the information we can collect are:

* **Name/alias and contact data** - We collect your email address and name/username.
* **Credentials** - We collect passwords and other security information used for authentication, anti-cheating, account access, security information, and other similar information.

Any information that you provide us will be thought of as accurate. If there are any changes to your information (particularly relating to emails), you must notify us and update your information.

### What's the privacy policy on gifts/donations?

* **Paypal** - We will only see your account/account ID and it’s association with your Paypal to your Hackerwars.io account and whatever other information you give us. The information on Paypal is stored under only Paypal’s policy:

* **Bitcoin** - Bitcoin is public and traceable on the bitcoin network. We can’t really see anything other than your bitcoin address and it’s association with your Hackerwars.io account.

### Information automatically collected

At an overview, we collect information such as IP addresses, browser and device characteristics/information. Much of this information is automatically collected when you visit the website.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit or use the website. This information does not reveal specific personal information such as your name and contact information but it may include device/host information and usage such as IP addresses, browser and cookies, device/host characteristics, operating system, language preferences, location, country, and information about how you use our information. This information will be primarily needed to ensure security on the website, prevent cheating, and for our analytics and reporting processes.

As stated previously and I want to reiterate, we do collect information through cookies.

### Information shared with third parties

We try to limit what information is shared but to provide you with services and to help manage the website, we do share some information legally.

Reasons for sharing may include legitimate business interests, legal obligations, and vital interests meaning we may use this information to investigate illegal activity, threats, and cheating.

**Third parties and services** - In addition, we may use your data to provide information to third party vendors and services. Examples include payment processing, data analytics, email delivery, hosting services, and marketing purposes. We may also allow selected third parties to do tracking activities to collect data interaction and content analytics.

**Business transfers** - We may also share and transfer information in the case of a merger, sale, financing, acquisition or part or of the whole website.

**Third party advertisers** - We may use a third party advertising company to serve ads when you visit the site. The company may use information about your visits to the website and other websites that contain cookies and tracking information to provide advertisements of goods and services that interest you.

**Other users** When you share or upload information in publicly viewable areas such as discord or in game logs or comments, your information may be viewed by all users and publicly distributed around the internet. In addition, other users will be able to view descriptions of your activity, communicate with you within our , and view your profile.

### Use of cookies

To put it simply, we may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.

### Information shared/transferred internationally

To start off, we may store, transfer, and process your information outside the country you reside. Our servers at the time of this policy creation are stored in the U.S. Please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us and by those third parties with whom we may share your personal information in your country and others around the world. If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, then these countries may not have data protection or other laws as comprehensive as those in your country. We will however take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law. Additional notes on third-party websites

We are not responsible for your safety, privacy, or protection of information that you provide to third-party provides who advertise. Hackerwars.io may contain advertisements from third parties not affiliated with us. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of the data you provide to these parties. We are not responsible for any content, security, privacy, or policies of any third party websites, applications, or services that may be linked on our site. You should review the policy on those third parties or contact them directly if you have any questions.

### How long do we keep your information?

We will keep your information for as long as necessary for the purpose of this privacy policy and for security, backup, and business reasons. When we permanently cease operations on this website and associates services and operations, we will either delete, anonymize, or if not immediately possible, we will store and isolate your information and work to delete it if possible.

### Do we collect information on minors?

We do not solicit or specifically target children under 18 years of age. We also don’t require there to input their age. But by using this website, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age or that you are the parent or guardian of the represented minor and consent to the minor’s use of this website. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected outside the scope of what’s listed in this privacy policy, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any such violation of this policy where data outside the scope of this policy is collected on minors under 18, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Privacy rights

**You may review, change, or terminate your existing account at any time.**

**You also have the right to request information we have on your account.**

#### Account Information

You can at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account. If you do so, Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files and backups to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Service and Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

You can also opt out of email subscriptions and marketing by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) until we setup an automated system to allow quick unsubscribes.

**Do not track features**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy policy.

**Do we make updates to this policy?**

Yes, we will try to update this policy to stay compliant with relevant laws. This website at the time of this policy writing is new and thus, we haven’t molded it completely to how we want it in the end. We will update this privacy policy when needed and updated versions will be indicated with a "revised" date. We also may notify you of notice of changes or email notifications. We encourage that you regularly read this privacy policy to stay informed.

**Who’s the Data Protection Officer/Person in charge of documentation?**

Username/Alias/Contact Name: Blackdawn  
[\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Contact us about this policy**

If you have any questions or comments relating to this policy, email us at [\[email protected\]](https://hackerwars.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
